[{"answer": "You believe this, don't you? That you're a vampire? You really think..", "docId": "Interview-with-the-Vampire.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "But I thought vampires didn't like the light", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What can I do to put you at ease? Shall we begin like my friend? I am born, I grow up. Or shall we begin when I was born to darkness, as I call it. That's really where we should start, don't you think", "docId": "Interview-with-the-Vampire.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Why should I lie? 1791 was the year it happened. I was twent", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Let's call that a start", "docId": "Interview-with-the-Vampire.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "You've just done it", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Don't worry. He was white trash, they come at two a penny. I dumped him in the swamp and untied the slave, licked his wounds clean", "docId": "Interview-with-the-Vampire.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " I wish I were. But if I were, what would I want with you", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I'm not interested in you. You disgust me. I'm interested in my own nature and know I can't trust you to tell me the truth about me", "docId": "Interview-with-the-Vampire.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I don't pretend to know", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Don't that place", "docId": "Interview-with-the-Vampire.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I'll put you in your coffin. Forever", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "He belongs with those reptiles, my friend. He deserved to die", "docId": "Interview-with-the-Vampire.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I did it for us, my friend. So we could be free", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Peasant rumors, superstitions about garlic, crosses, stakes in the hear, all that", "docId": "Interview-with-the-Vampire.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Fictions, my friend. The vulgar fictions of a demented Irishman... So we repaired to that place..", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "my friend, you torture yourself", "docId": "Interview-with-the-Vampire.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You are more beautiful than any of them", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Death is no respecter of age. He can come any time, any place. Need I tell you what fate has in store for you", "docId": "Interview-with-the-Vampire.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "And if you take that chance and live, what is your fate? The humpbacked toothless visage of old age", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "You don't want to answer... Two vampires from the new world, come to guide us into the new era as all we love slowly rots and fades away", "docId": "Interview-with-the-Vampire.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "If there were a leader, I would be the one", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Nothing if not vampires..", "docId": "Interview-with-the-Vampire.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Surely you know the one who made you..", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Who made us what we are", "docId": "Interview-with-the-Vampire.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "But the one who made him, who made the one who made him, the source of all this evil..", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Then God does not exist..", "docId": "Interview-with-the-Vampire.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "And no vampire here has discourse with God or the Devil", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "You read my thoughts", "docId": "Interview-with-the-Vampire.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "A name I don't want to say again", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Do you think I would let them harm you", "docId": "Interview-with-the-Vampire.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Love holds you to me. And we are in danger, not you", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "But why", "docId": "Interview-with-the-Vampire.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Then blame the one who made her..", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I could give you reasons. Her silence. Her youth. It's forbidden to make so young, so helpless, that cannot survive on its own", "docId": "Interview-with-the-Vampire.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Did you kill this vampire who made you both? Is that why you won't say his name? that place thinks you did", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "Interview-with-the-Vampire.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I knew. I rescued you, didn't I? From the terrible dawn", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "I have to go now Lestat..", "docId": "Interview-with-the-Vampire.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Yes. I remember..", "qsentId": 40}]